[Music]
[Applause]
Wow bro now I'm doing that anymore
we want to talk about that we are not
packing it because hacking is bad that's
right man
don't be a hacker
you
[Music]
school refactor
and write a test on a haircut - that
guys
so order McDonald's she's gonna be here
to bed
12:20 straight keep the image around
Oh Mike I don't like that I can't factor
this out nice
far as it draws the matches
and we could just return the image just
and compute like this either this works
I'm not happy right now
you know know who told you you could be
none I've clearly returned image right
there does that return earlier oh yeah
yes it's already a zero it's fine
the way I'm drawing the annotations is
wrong I just don't like the way this is
like factor
like this refactor more who followed
this roof actor
another type object has no attribute
sorry sighs I shouldn't be in there
really
anyway
basically I paint the car
[Music]
yes
that's why
I wasn't drunk watching the guy drive
the clock all of this video
all right Richie's does anybody have a
good I'm trying to okay I'll tell you
what I'm trying to do I'm trying to make
it work in the rendered environment
wonder who I'll work out this guy's car
not well of all the snow moves but yeah
so that's what fake slams gonna be I'm I
have to do that refactor first look
McDonald's get V you soon
I got to make chickens and a small
french fries I'm not gonna eat the bun
of the make chickens I'm just gonna eat
chicken part and the lettuce and then
the french fries because then I can eat
the French fries you can't eat the bun
and the French fries that's Savage
like one wheeler or unity you know I'm
talking about
works for Windows
the beautifulest flower box
I want a game engine
what is this
it's a nice looking couch bro I can nap
on that couch
oh my foods here almost here I know
you're almost over
I know twitch Slim cuz it's tomorrow
like this have good demos it's amazing
how you just trust like this never
mind I can't open it because from all
identify developed what's the key you
press control don't have to go into God
no I'm sorry like security or something
no I think any jetskis bros I'm never
doing security again I forgot how much I
hated it actually canceled this is
really old really old
oh okay I don't want any of this you
know what you know what guys you know
what I have on my github you don't might
be the perfect yeah we'll use one of my
old projects low-quality raytracer
should we use low-quality raytracer
it's a good project
joke
this coat looks terrible here I mean it
did warn that it was low quality little
paulie's in right now I know it'll be
Polly kids
oh my fools here I'll be back
oh yeah we got mint chicken
I shouldn't have to write this
no they know what fries I got fries no
order with dolls
I ordered a fries a McChicken and apple
pie
and then brought me a mix chicken a
fries and another fries and I was like
where's my apple pie but then I just
went to sleep and didn't complain I
never learned how to be better
mmm savage all right
yeah
there's no Milan sauce why don't you
become why you something out use PI
OpenGL yeah yeah this is gonna work
I'm gonna doing Python 3 2 cuz we put on
three now
what the hell
why am i watching an ad right now
I don't even know the sad bunny who
wants the bun press a button by accident
I lost chopped some reason I went to an
ad see how this looks okay you can pie
gave a perfect high the example app
works
my Laura
well okay a few things we have to figure
out how to write in class
now on demo videos and uh big don't you
have broadband or you want dial-up is
anyone still on dial-up they still make
that I bet even in sub-saharan Africa
they're like whoa bro I haven't seen
dial-up and forever Magic Man
what's an agent
what's an adit
is this a political person I don't know
any political people hey spot mercy well
I solve my problem how I'm gonna render
so very strong these four tabs or spaces
not offensive tactics tabs are
incredibly
Savage
being McHale raincode this is the life
families hanging out today I bought nice
clothes
I got hecka
this looks hard
oh wow this looks hard
Goliath
and glide
I'm call you political I just said that
sounds like a political thing Majid pie
isn't that a political thing he's an
American particle than I think so is the
right country what about America oh who
remembers we started so many years ago
nobody remembers things like that oh I
just mean what as well mm-hmm ordeal
Mike you my beautiful cube doesn't make
sense but yet when I run that it works
that doesn't make sense no no that
doesn't make sense
display 127 importation
I've never done in my life to help
Barbies oh my god perfectly clear if you
ever thought I did something to help
normies that was a lie this Penta
sativas mostly not cool you know the
internet used to not have normies on it
and he used to be nice and the normies
showed up on the internet and that's
what we are today let's ignore me ruin
internet with their Instagram follower
or snapchat likes and Twitter tweet
bowls and whatever normies ruin the
internet the internet was a great thing
keep hacking the lead okay segmentation
fault the left that's great
what normos don't know about McDonald's
why why you sedimentation vault 11 folks
I need glutes
let's do glass oh it doesn't crash I'm
so happy
what up bro your bro got a few fries but
guys mix no wife can subscribe to my
twitch I need money
bitch twitch can't even pay for the food
I eat wild and twitching it's gonna have
to be canceled canceled canceled
canceled
image oh gee L read pixels that's what
I'm talking about oh thank you thank you
boys on Yolo thank you
you guys never watch the cam girls on my
free cams so we shall have any contest
like that yeah slowly I want that
brow now so he's gonna be relevant today
I think I think I might be punching down
my function down oh yeah look at that is
that a real image let's say wait a
second why do I need RGBA
no very suspicious
sighs nope bad nor me I was four because
of the egg
don't forget the a nice oh call it paint
[Laughter]
like this disgusting supply boy
$13 what is this
that was disgusting
are you regret fighting that scam
related to college what a scam what
college kids just be good at things the
best people I know it things didn't go
to college no almost tell me today that
I should wash my sheets I got new sheets
it was like you should wash them before
you sleep on them because they're
covered with chemicals and then I was
like but I am chemicals what do you
think I'm made of preservatives what do
you think I'm made of they're depressed
I'll do that
they don't have rice all its open at
12:02 a.m. is McDonald's 10 bar food
it's probably worth to mcdonald do
anything melamine calories are in it
McDonald's they tell you the calories
and the Nutrition Facts which aren't
that bad bro doesn't know that bad bro
I'm just putting that out there bro
yo you know what I was thinking I'm not
on a healthy guy stop with that
stop health saving me I don't want money
I don't know what I would buy that's
right I give zero match the other
day something about when you start
giving about things don't take
them from you they will but you know
what they can never take her away from
you free software all right where was I
I'm kind of tired
hey that McDonald's and I'm come tired
I'm not like making a podcast let me
tell you if I'm making a podcast right
so let's say I want to do this right so
who's gonna be on my podcast this is
just gonna be me talking about or
am I gonna get guests then I got an
email the guests okay so you gotta like
email probably let's say 10 people for
every given you get three replies and
then like two of them say they want to
do it and then one of them finally comes
on your show so you gotta you gotta
email 10 people to get one now I gotta
schedule a time for them to come down oh
they're gonna come down to my office
they're gonna be late they're gonna want
to make small talk I'm gonna put them in
a room with a microphone and I'm gonna
have to think of a script I'm gonna have
to ask them questions I'm gonna have to
act like what the CEG's most
interesting in the world and then
I'm gonna put it on a podcast nobody's
even gonna listen to it then I'm right
all right fine fine fine I gotta work on
my brand right so let's make a Twitter
and a Facebook and then you know we got
it we gotta get that get that social
gotta get the Instagram maybe maybe I'll
have a controversial guest or maybe I'll
have Steve man
Podcast right and at least they'll be
some outrage I'll get some clicks for
that for a little while but guys this
all sounds terrible why would I want to
do this now right that's my rant about
podcasts surrender or really living its
own
yeah yeah and then oh okay all right
let's keep playing let's keep playing
so then my podcast gets popular now Wow
man is podcast really great like people
are discovering it and it's all
cool but then like you have like one or
two episodes that aren't really that
great or maybe it's not even that
they're not that great but people just
start saying that - like man remember
the old podcast remember when it was
good wish you would keep making a
podcast like that maybe you wanna you
know stop making the podcast always
you're gonna get his hate man you're
just gonna get hate from all the people
oh man why'd you stop making the podcast
I'm gonna come to your house my
up that's what's gonna happen why
would you make a podcast nigga with guys
let me tell you something out this
twister we got 33 people right now if
this twitch stream ever got popular
hahaha you better believe we gotta make
it go away cuz that would make it shitty
and that's what happened to the Internet
no no no a couple of 10 I went on a date
with alright did that girl which night
was that I don't know they're kind of
stopped hanging out with one girl been
hanging out with southern girl you know
whole life why do you think normies love
the thug life in County does lemon does
life is pretty awesome
I think normies live the most bitch-ass
life like to be honest here's what I
said just something I was thinking about
about Collin who owns a Honda Civic I
don't know apparently there's a lot of
them but like I don't know I don't know
a Honda Civic
it's nice car but like died role I'm not
tall human telling you the complete
truth about why I would never start a
like the girl all right use my advice
about that right you know sometime you
hear from people ah
insel man I'm involuntarily celibate and
here's what I asked them how might be
girls did you ask to have sex with you
today if the answer is zero little
don't be creepy about it but like so
yeah there you go that's what this
turned into that's what I'm saying
or at least how many women did you
interact with today who could there
could be a potential of you sleeping
together you get that number up that's
one of your key business metrics you
could track that with logs you
could you could put it in it
elasticsearch maybe throw a cabana front
end on that you could look at your
growth numbers you're doing so well you
could probably even get VC funding VC's
love growth no man which doesn't matter
at all get VC funding all right oh yeah
trying to make this work but it was
complaining that I had too much of luck
does work a lot redisplay needed for
window one but no display
tree back into this blight class and
make this DIY game
definitely not know if I ever feel like
you're sucking up to me in an interview
I'll throw you out so fast don't say any
of this man if anyone ever come to
work for me who talked like I talked on
Twitch's I've never hired process we do
that
yeah it's in a process
and should we tolerate insults of Python
on this channel oh well who remembers
the guy got banned yesterday I thought
his Python is ugly look is it
what's up nice-looking language now I'm
up time to think about this this is
interesting
crash hey crash
No
don't work a threat
in Madison College how much I care about
tools back in my day tools and people
that you made fun oh you know well like
that guy's a tool man oh don't give me
the about oh I hate this my game my
game work STL - problem example Mike you
there's some reason I tried to write
this with SDL because I was like being a
cute stupid
my game works alright let's just change
the display QD class
did I try to use pygame and I got like
fed up with it for some reason
Oh God gets screen size and that's a
nice one
all right self surface hey why are a
surfer nice way to do this
oh it's this problem I vaguely remember
this this might have just have to do
with events actually yeah okay it works
now I mean the colors frog but that's
okay what is that
colors
that's absurd
do you kitty pryde no we do anything
else tonight
it might be what we're doing tonight
it's kind of like there's things to do
tomorrow make this work first then I'll
be happy that doesn't work when I'm
incoming renderer so this is exactly the
same thing that happened before I did
always wonder why the colors were
backwards that did kind of answer that
long-standing bugs and twitch left
well maybe it'll all be a little as
Jackie now hopefully I don't like any of
that SDL stuff but you're telling me
that renderer still doesn't work
that's man redisplay needed for
window wat so basically I can't make pi
Gabe hmm and glut work at the same time
all right that's it that's a little
weird which streaming today if you want
to be a winner you should be happy no is
that true
a winner's happy
how are you gonna ask something like
that you got to ask is that true does
life balance help you with success -
like what are you calling success
remember when I've told you about having
a successful podcast is that really the
life you want a lot of success is some
scam that was just like like they like
tricked you into like like the
advertisers want you to succeed so you
can buy more crap success I mean yeah
you know a sock so what does work know
why it doesn't work
I could use my process I could have a
rendering process that does the
off-screen blot oh yeah we do pull
requests if you want to fix that a poor
customer check but you see where I'm
going with this I want to write a little
renderer get a few things up I want to
make slam work the other way I'm going
to sleep goodnight twitchy's you got to
we let's see we ate McDonald's and wrote
a non-existent crappy renderer let's
watch the cube rotate one we put the
cube oh so nice cube also nice peace
bros look at that beautiful cube
beautiful cube
wash your cube rotate